# Yoav Danieli

# Summary:

I am a software enthusiast with experience developing software solutions from design to production. Extensive knowledge in Full-stack web applications. I love solving algorithmic problems, coding challenges and optimization issues. My goal is to sharpen my technological skills and gain knowledge and experience by working and interacting with top talent engineers and product experts.

#### Education

2015 - 2019 B.Sc. Computer Science, Technion. Dean's List honors received.

# **Professional Experience**

# 2021 - 2022 Prycto - Full-Stack Developer

- Developed an inner product that was in charge of allocating and liquidating crypto-assets between different crypto wallets, bank accounts, and cryptocurrency exchange accounts. The frontend of the product was written with React and the backend with Typescript.
- Designed and developed a new microservice architecture for the trading platform used by the company. The platform is written in Rust.

# 2019 - 2021 <u>Vonage Holdings Corp - Full-Stack Developer</u>

- Developed VBC "Vonage Business Communication" A Web and Electron application written in Vue.js and Node.js, Enabling businesses to find communication solutions for a variety of needs.
- Developed Vonage's App Center a Microservices infrastructure built using Serverless Framework, that allows external applications to be integrated with VBC.
- Collaborating with various teams both in and outside the company in order to learn new tools and technologies to integrate with the product.
- Working in a cloud-based environment, continuously improving the CI/CD pipeline for both our client-side and server-side applications.

#### 2017 - 2019 <u>Intel Corporation - Cyber Security Researcher (student position)</u>

- Developed and utilized tools to provide security evaluation for Intel SGX on SKL, ICL, and ICX.
- Code reviewing Intel's new products as part of the task team searching for vulnerabilities and when found, finding a solution of protection and preventing more vulnerabilities.

#### 2015 - 2016 ASAT Technion - Workshop Instructor for 'Intro to Computer Science and C Language'

• Supported students in understanding the fundamentals of Computer Science and C Language.

#### Computer Application Knowledge

Javascript | Node.js | Typescript | Vue.js | AWS | Serverless FW | Python | C/C++ | Bash | SQL | HTML | CSS | MongoDB | Docker | Terraform | Rust | React

# Personal Projects

- A Platform for automated trading Developed a platform that automates trading strategies. The
  platform is integrated with an American broker and can be used to deploy strategies on NYSE,
  Nasdaq, and CME.
- <u>Predicting cryptocurrency values based on a mixture of datasets</u> Developed an LSTM network model with Keras framework, to predict cryptocurrency values based on varying sources of data.
- <u>Competitive Programming</u> Attended a workshop for competitive programming sponsored by Google, Taking part in coding competitions occasionally.

# Military Service and Extracurricular Activities

2014 - 2016 PET (Psychometric Entrance Test) Teacher at Kidum Group.

2010 - 2013 Full service in the Israeli armored corps as a Tank Commander and recruits coordinator.

2009 - 2010 Volunteered in Tel Baruch, a boarding house for children with social and economic problems.

# Languages

Hebrew - Mother tongue | English - Native Level

# Contact Information:

Email: yoav.danieli91@gmail.com

LinkedIn: <a href="www.linkedin.com/in/yoav-danieli">www.linkedin.com/in/yoav-danieli</a> WhatsApp: <a href="https://wa.me/972549798034">https://wa.me/972549798034</a>